webstat.com 2013-06-04

# WebSTAT :: Privacy Policy

|  |   
---  
  
|   |    
---|---  
**Commitment to Privacy**  
WebSTAT respects the sensitive nature of the information you provide us. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your personal information while maximizing your access to our services, both paid and free.  
   
This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive from you when you sign up for an account. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully because it governs how we use the information you submit to us. If this Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the information you have submitted to us in a manner that is inconsistent with the Privacy Policy under which the information was originally collected.   
   
**How We Identify Who You Are**  
We track web sites, which are often maintained by several different people. When you sign up with us, we will use the email you provided as the primary line of communication. We will recognize any requests from your email account as being from you.  
   
The ownership of web sites also frequently changes, and hence we will also accept the URL as identification. We will recognize any change to the web site as being done by you. Any email from your website domain or listed on your site we will recognize as being from you.  
   
**How We Use Your Information**  
When you sign up for an account on WebSTAT, you provide us with your website name, website URL, name, time zone and email address. The time zone is used to report statistics and the name is used to address you. The URL and email address is to identify you and contact you. Email addresses are utilized only to notify users of significant changes, to address support concerns, or to resolve abuse issues.   
   
If you sign up for a Premium account, you will additionally provide us with your address, phone number, website category and fax number. The fax number is optional. We will use this information to contact you if there are any problems with your account. If you pay with a credit card, we will collect the credit card information, including the name and address on the card, the credit card number and the expiration date. If you pay with some other method, we will collect the name and address of the person paying for the account.  
   
**How We Do NOT Use Your Information**  
WebSTAT does not provide or sell any sensitive user information to any third party, including email addresses, credit card numbers, billing information, street addresses, and phone numbers.  WebSTAT does not promote, support, or tolerate email spam!  
   
Credit Card Information  
WebSTAT is very careful with your credit card information. When you enter your credit card information, we will do so over a secure connection. We will not display your credit card information anywhere when you log in, so you can allow people to see your statistics without sharing your credit card information. We will not send your credit card information over email. If you need to send it to us, it is suggested that you submit over our [secure connection](https://secure.webstat.com/secure.php).  
   
Your Statistics  
Your statistics are only available to you and those with whom you have shared the password. WebSTAT employees will also be able to view your statistics for support and billing issues. We will not share your statistics with any third party.  
   
If you choose to give your account public access, then anyone will be able to view your statistics that follows a public link or has your site id number. They will not be able to see any of your contact information.  
   
**Cookies**  
Cookies are used to facilitate page path tracking and statistics on returning and unique visitors. They are not used to collect personally identifiable information about visitors. WebSTAT uses sessional and permanent cookies to help track your visitor's traffic patterns through your site. Session cookies expire within a short period of time or when you close your web browser.  
   
With most Internet browsers, you can block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. It is also possible to delete all cookies from your computer's hard drive. Many cookies can be deleted with no ill effect, but some will contain information that will make your subsequent visits to certain websites more useful.  
   
**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions, please **[let us know](http://support.webstat.com/?_a=tickets&_m=submit).**  
  |
